Amy Hollinger

Cherry Hill, NJ 08034 | 609-204-7078 | amyahaha@gmail.com LinkedIn Profile: www.linkedin.com/in/amyAhollinger

Portfolio: https://thegetoutgirl.github.io | Github Profile: https://github.com/thegetoutgirl

Summary

Full stack web developer with previous experience in sales administration, STEM Education, project and event management. Team player, problem solver with a break-it-until-it-works mentality, with focus on user experience and data management.

Technical Skills

Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, React, ES5/ES6/ES7, Java

Applications: AJAX, Bootstrap/ReactStrap, Express, Git/Github, Materialize, Material UI, Mustache/Handlebars,

MySQL, MongoDB, NodeJS, OAuth, WordPress

Projects

collabHub

Github link: https://github.com/thegetoutgirl/collabHub | Deployed App: https://collab-hub.herokuapp.com/ An app to connect developers with each other for future collaborations. Users sign in and search user database for others to match skillsets. My responsibilities: Search page, contact feature, and link Github API to user profile page. Tools / languages used: HTML/CSS, Javascript, MySQL, Materialize, PassportJS, Handlebars, Github API.

TossUp!

Github link: https://github.com/thegetoutgirl/Tossup | Deployed App: https://tossup-election-sim.herokuapp.com/ An election simulator game. Users can name candidates and "run elections", saving candidates and results, and compete against their friends. My responsibilities: UX lead, sign in, user database creation, PassportJS authentication. Tools / languages used: JavaScript, React, MongoDB, Material UI, D3, PassportJS.

Work History

Program Specialist, STEM Education

Girl Scouts of Central & Southern NJ. Cherry Hill, NJ. 2015 – 2020

Responsible for budgeting, marketing, and overseeing registrations for Science and Technology programs for girls in grades K-12. Oversee grants and coordinate programs with STEM vendors and instructors. Created trainings and resources for 2000 adult volunteers. Accomplishments include creation of multiple large-scale STEM events, including an annual conference serving over 400 girls and adults.

Lead Development Specialist

Automotive Resources International (Holman Enterprises). Mt. Laurel, NJ. 2013 – 2015 Identify potential clients within sales target markets, including utilities, construction, specialty truck fleets, and companies with large motor pools or sales fleets. Report on pipeline progress across 20+ sales regions weekly.

Team Lead/Underwriting Liaison

Corporate Call Center. Blue Bell, PA. 2010 – 2012

Responsible for supervising 20 agents in sales and customer service for Medicare supplement and prescription plans. Responsible for supporting sales training manager with on-the-spot coaching, supplemental training, and maintaining Knowledge Base for licensed agents. Team maintained 85%+ inbound sales success rate over two seasons.

Education

University of Pennsylvania College of Liberal and Professional Studies (LPS), Philadelphia PA. Full stack developer certificate (Completed April 2020)

Towson University, Towson, MD. BA Communications; Minor in German